var jp_targets = [
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u65b0\u805e\u3067\u7d39\u4ecb\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\u305f\n\n\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5c4a\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":1,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"14 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":1,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u805e\u3067\u7d39\u4ecb\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\u305f\n\n\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5c4a\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":1,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"13 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":1,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5c4a\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":1,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"13 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27,
        "Group":1,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u304a\u6bcd\u3055\u3093\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3053\u3069\u3082\u304b\u3089\u3068\u3066\u3082\u597d\u304b\n\n\u308c\u3066\u3044\u308b\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u713c\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":2,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"8 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":2,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u304a\u6bcd\u3055\u3093\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3053\u3069\u3082\u304b\u3089\u3068\u3066\u3082\u597d\u304b\n\n\u308c\u3066\u3044\u308b\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u713c\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":2,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"14 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":2,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u304a\u6bcd\u3055\u3093\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u304a\u83d3\u5b50\u3092",
        "verb":"\u713c\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":2,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"5 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":12,
        "Group":2,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3053\u3068\u306f",
        "np1":"\u65b0\u5165\u793e\u54e1\u3067\u306f\u624b\u304c\u5c4a\u304b\n\n\u306a\u3044\u7f8e\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d0\u30c3\u30b0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":3,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"8 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":3,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3053\u3068\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7f8e\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u5165\u793e\u54e1\u3067\u306f\u624b\u304c\u5c4a\u304b\n\n\u306a\u3044\u30d0\u30c3\u30b0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":3,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"9 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":3,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3053\u3068\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7f8e\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d0\u30c3\u30b0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":3,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"15 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":28,
        "Group":3,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5927\u7d71\u9818\u306f",
        "np1":"\u56fd\u6c11\u304b\u3089\u652f\u6301\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u306a\u3044\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u8b70\u6848\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":4,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"10 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":4,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5927\u7d71\u9818\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u56fd\u6c11\u304b\u3089\u652f\u6301\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u306a\u3044\u8b70\u6848\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":4,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"10 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":4,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5927\u7d71\u9818\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8b70\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u8b70\u6848\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":4,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"13 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":4,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307f\u3061\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u306a\u304b\u306a\u304b\u7d50\u69cb\u9762\u767d\u3044\u5e97\n\n\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5c0f\u8aac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6ce8\u6587\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":5,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"7 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":5,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307f\u3061\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5e97\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u306a\u304b\u306a\u304b\u7d50\u69cb\u9762\u767d\u3044\u5c0f\n\n\u8aac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6ce8\u6587\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":5,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"10 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":5,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307f\u3061\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5e97\u54e1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5c0f\u8aac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6ce8\u6587\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":5,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"5 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":5,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u65b0\u805e\u8a18\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u9078\u624b\u306e\u9593\u3067\u5642\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u308b\u30b3\u30fc\u30c1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u79d8\u5bc6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8a71\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":6,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"9 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24,
        "Group":6,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u65b0\u805e\u8a18\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u30b3\u30fc\u30c1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u9078\u624b\u306e\u9593\u3067\u5642\u3055\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u308b\u79d8\u5bc6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8a71\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":6,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"11 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":6,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u65b0\u805e\u8a18\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u30b3\u30fc\u30c1\u306b",
        "np2":"\u79d8\u5bc6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8a71\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":6,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"15 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":6,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7fd4\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u753a\u306e\u4eba\u306a\u3089\u8ab0\u3067\u3082\u77e5\u3063\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308b\u6709\u540d\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u7f8e\u8853\u9928\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":7,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"14 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":7,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7fd4\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u6709\u540d\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u753a\u306e\u4eba\u306a\u3089\u8ab0\u3067\u3082\u77e5\u3063\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308b\u7f8e\u8853\u9928\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":7,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"14 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27,
        "Group":7,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7fd4\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u6709\u540d\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u7f8e\u8853\u9928\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":7,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"10 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":7,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u8001\u4eba\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3059\u3063\u304b\u308a\u5fd8\u308c\u3089\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u305f\u89aa\u621a\u306b",
        "np2":"\u571f\u5730\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3086\u305a\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":8,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"9 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":8,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u8001\u4eba\u306f",
        "np1":"\u89aa\u621a\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3059\u3063\u304b\u308a\u5fd8\u308c\u3089\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u305f\u8ca1\u7523\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3086\u305a\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":8,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"5 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":8,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u8001\u4eba\u306f",
        "np1":"\u89aa\u621a\u306b",
        "np2":"\u8ca1\u7523\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3086\u305a\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":8,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"7 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":8,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3088\u3057\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3069\u3046\u3082\u3042\u3093\u307e\u308a\u898b\u3070\u3048\n\n\u306e\u3057\u306a\u3044\u5f7c\u6c0f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5199\u771f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6295\u3052\u3064\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":9,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"5 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":9,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3088\u3057\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5f7c\u6c0f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3069\u3046\u3082\u3042\u3093\u307e\u308a\u898b\u3070\u3048\n\n\u306e\u3057\u306a\u3044\u5199\u771f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6295\u3052\u3064\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":9,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"14 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":9,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3088\u3057\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5f7c\u6c0f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5199\u771f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6295\u3052\u3064\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":9,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"13 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":9,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u66f2\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8ab0\u3082\u3092\u5fc3\u304b\u3089\u611f\u52d5\u3055\u305b\n\n\u308b\u6b4c\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d0\u30e9\u30fc\u30c9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u66f8\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":10,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"5 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14,
        "Group":10,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u66f2\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u6b4c\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u8ab0\u3082\u3092\u5fc3\u304b\u3089\u611f\u52d5\u3055\u305b\n\n\u308b\u30d0\u30e9\u30fc\u30c9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u66f8\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":10,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"10 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":10,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u66f2\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u6b4c\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d0\u30e9\u30fc\u30c9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u66f8\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":10,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"14 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":10,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u305f\u304b\u3057\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u8f29\u306b",
        "np2":"\u307f\u3093\u306a\u304b\u3089\u3068\u3066\u3082\u89aa\u3057\n\n\u307e\u308c\u3066\u3044\u308b\u6f2b\u753b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":11,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"10 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18,
        "Group":11,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u305f\u304b\u3057\u306f",
        "np1":"\u307f\u3093\u306a\u304b\u3089\u3068\u3066\u3082\u89aa\u3057\n\n\u307e\u308c\u3066\u3044\u308b\u5148\u8f29\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6f2b\u753b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":11,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"6 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":11,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u305f\u304b\u3057\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u8f29\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6f2b\u753b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":11,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"12 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":11,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7de8\u96c6\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3061\u307e\u305f\u3067\u3082\u3066\u306f\u3084\u3055\u308c\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308b\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"CD\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":12,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"10 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":12,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7de8\u96c6\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3061\u307e\u305f\u3067\u3082\u3066\u306f\u3084\u3055\u308c\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308bCD\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":12,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"5 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14,
        "Group":12,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7de8\u96c6\u8005\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"CD\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3042\u3052\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":12,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"14 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":28,
        "Group":12,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u304d\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4f55\u3068\u306a\u304f\u3069\u3053\u304b\u5909\u308f\u3063\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308b\u53cb\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u96d1\u8a8c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cb8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":13,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"9 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":13,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u304d\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u53cb\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4f55\u3068\u306a\u304f\u3069\u3053\u304b\u5909\u308f\u3063\n\n\u3066\u3044\u308b\u96d1\u8a8c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cb8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":13,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"11 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":13,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u304d\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u53cb\u4eba\u306b",
        "np2":"\u96d1\u8a8c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cb8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":13,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"13 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24,
        "Group":13,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e97\u54e1\u306f",
        "np1":"\u601d\u308f\u305a\u4eba\u76ee\u3092\u3072\u3044\u3066\u3057\n\n\u307e\u3046\u5973\u6027\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30b9\u30ab\u30fc\u30c8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3059\u3059\u3081\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":14,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"8 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15,
        "Group":14,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e97\u54e1\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5973\u6027\u306b",
        "np2":"\u601d\u308f\u305a\u4eba\u76ee\u3092\u3072\u3044\u3066\u3057\n\n\u307e\u3046\u30b9\u30ab\u30fc\u30c8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3059\u3059\u3081\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":14,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"7 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":14,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e97\u54e1\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5973\u6027\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30b9\u30ab\u30fc\u30c8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3059\u3059\u3081\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":14,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"10 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":14,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5065\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5730\u5143\u3067\u306f\u3088\u304f\u77e5\u3089\u308c\u3066\n\n\u3044\u308b\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d3\u30fc\u30eb\u3092",
        "verb":"\u914d\u9054\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":15,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"15 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":15,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5065\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5730\u5143\u3067\u306f\u3088\u304f\u77e5\u3089\u308c\u3066\n\n\u3044\u308b\u30d3\u30fc\u30eb\u3092",
        "verb":"\u914d\u9054\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":15,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"13 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24,
        "Group":15,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5065\u592a\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30d3\u30fc\u30eb\u3092",
        "verb":"\u914d\u9054\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":15,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"13 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":15,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3069\u3046\u898b\u3066\u3082\u3042\u3093\u307e\u308a\u3071\n\n\u3063\u3068\u3057\u306a\u3044\u52a9\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30ab\u30e1\u30e9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3084\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":16,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"12 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":16,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u52a9\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3069\u3046\u898b\u3066\u3082\u3042\u3093\u307e\u308a\u3071\n\n\u3063\u3068\u3057\u306a\u3044\u30ab\u30e1\u30e9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3084\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":16,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"12 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":16,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u4f5c\u5bb6\u306f",
        "np1":"\u52a9\u624b\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30ab\u30e1\u30e9\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3084\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":16,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"15 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27,
        "Group":16,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3055\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5b50\u4f9b\u9054\u306e\u9593\u3067\u4eba\u6c17\u306e\u3042\n\n\u308b\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":17,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"11 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":17,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3055\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5b50\u4f9b\u9054\u306e\u9593\u3067\u4eba\u6c17\u306e\u3042\n\n\u308b\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":17,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"11 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":17,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u307e\u3055\u3053\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30b2\u30fc\u30e0\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":17,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"7 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":17,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u63a2\u5075\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4e38\u4e00\u65e5\u4e2d\u8ffd\u8de1\u3057\u305f\u7537\u306b",
        "np2":"\u30ef\u30b4\u30f3\u8eca\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5f15\u304d\u6e21\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":18,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"6 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":18,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u63a2\u5075\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7537\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4e38\u4e00\u65e5\u4e2d\u8ffd\u8de1\u3057\u305f\u8eca\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5f15\u304d\u6e21\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":18,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"12 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":18,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u63a2\u5075\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7537\u306b",
        "np2":"\u8eca\u3092",
        "verb":"\u5f15\u304d\u6e21\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":18,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"11 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":18,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u3084\u304b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u524d\u304b\u3089\u4f55\u3068\u306a\u304f\u6c17\u306b\u306a\n\n\u3063\u3066\u3044\u305f\u540c\u7d1a\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u60a9\u307f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6253\u3061\u660e\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":19,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"14 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":19,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u3084\u304b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u540c\u7d1a\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u524d\u304b\u3089\u4f55\u3068\u306a\u304f\u6c17\u306b\u306a\n\n\u3063\u3066\u3044\u305f\u60a9\u307f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6253\u3061\u660e\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":19,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"7 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":19,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u3042\u3084\u304b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u540c\u7d1a\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u60a9\u307f\u3092",
        "verb":"\u6253\u3061\u660e\u3051\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":19,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"5 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":10,
        "Group":19,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e02\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u9577\u3044\u635c\u67fb\u306e\u672b\u767a\u898b\u3055\u308c\n\n\u305f\u5c11\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5c0f\u72ac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30d7\u30ec\u30bc\u30f3\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":20,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"15 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27,
        "Group":20,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e02\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5c11\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u9577\u3044\u635c\u67fb\u306e\u672b\u767a\u898b\u3055\u308c\n\n\u305f\u5c0f\u72ac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30d7\u30ec\u30bc\u30f3\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":20,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"13 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":20,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u5e02\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5c11\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5c0f\u72ac\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30d7\u30ec\u30bc\u30f3\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":20,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"7 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":20,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u306e\u307c\u308b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u65e5\u9280\u5ea7\u3067\u5076\u7136\u898b\u304b\u3051\n\n\u305f\u5973\u306e\u5b50\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6307\u8f2a\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8d08\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":21,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"8 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":21,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u306e\u307c\u308b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5973\u306e\u5b50\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5148\u65e5\u9280\u5ea7\u3067\u5076\u7136\u898b\u304b\u3051\n\n\u305f\u6307\u8f2a\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8d08\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":21,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"15 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":21,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u306e\u307c\u308b\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5973\u306e\u5b50\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6307\u8f2a\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8d08\u3063\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":21,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"15 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":21,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7537\u306e\u4e57\u5ba2\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3055\u3063\u304d\u3069\u3046\u3057\u3066\u3082\u898b\u3064\n\n\u304b\u3089\u306a\u304b\u3063\u305f\u8eca\u638c\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5207\u7b26\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":22,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"12 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":22,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7537\u306e\u4e57\u5ba2\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8eca\u638c\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3055\u3063\u304d\u3069\u3046\u3057\u3066\u3082\u898b\u3064\n\n\u304b\u3089\u306a\u304b\u3063\u305f\u5207\u7b26\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":22,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"5 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18,
        "Group":22,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u7537\u306e\u4e57\u5ba2\u306f",
        "np1":"\u8eca\u638c\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5207\u7b26\u3092",
        "verb":"\u898b\u305b\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":22,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"5 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18,
        "Group":22,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b21\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4eca\u307e\u3067\u8ab0\u3082\u805e\u3044\u305f\u3053\u3068\n\n\u304c\u306a\u3044DJ\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u66f2\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30ea\u30af\u30a8\u30b9\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":23,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"7 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13,
        "Group":23,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b21\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"DJ\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4eca\u307e\u3067\u8ab0\u3082\u805e\u3044\u305f\u3053\u3068\n\n\u304c\u306a\u3044\u65b0\u66f2\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30ea\u30af\u30a8\u30b9\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":23,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"5 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13,
        "Group":23,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b21\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"DJ\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u66f2\u3092",
        "verb":"\u30ea\u30af\u30a8\u30b9\u30c8\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":23,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"15 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":23,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u90e8\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4f1a\u8b70\u3067\u8a55\u5224\u304c\u826f\u304f\u306a\u304b\n\n\u3063\u305f\u90e8\u9577\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4f01\u753b\u66f8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8fd4\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":24,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"13 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23,
        "Group":24,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u90e8\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u90e8\u9577\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4f1a\u8b70\u3067\u8a55\u5224\u304c\u826f\u304f\u306a\u304b\n\n\u3063\u305f\u4f01\u753b\u66f8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8fd4\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":24,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"13 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26,
        "Group":24,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u90e8\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u90e8\u9577\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4f01\u753b\u66f8\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8fd4\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":24,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"8 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13,
        "Group":24,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6d0b\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5973\u306e\u5b50\u306a\u3089\u3060\u308c\u3082\u304c\u3042\n\n\u3053\u304c\u308c\u308b\u7d33\u58eb\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6d0b\u670d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u304a\u306d\u3060\u308a\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":25,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"10 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":25,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6d0b\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7d33\u58eb\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5973\u306e\u5b50\u306a\u3089\u3060\u308c\u3082\u304c\u3042\n\n\u3053\u304c\u308c\u308b\u6d0b\u670d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u304a\u306d\u3060\u308a\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":25,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"12 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19,
        "Group":25,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6d0b\u5b50\u306f",
        "np1":"\u7d33\u58eb\u306b",
        "np2":"\u6d0b\u670d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u304a\u306d\u3060\u308a\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":25,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"12 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":25,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u793e\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u90e8\u5185\u3067\u3082\u7d50\u69cb\u4eba\u6c17\u306e\u3042\n\n\u308b\u79d8\u66f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u4eba\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":26,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"12 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":26,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u793e\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u79d8\u66f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u90e8\u5185\u3067\u3082\u7d50\u69cb\u4eba\u6c17\u306e\u3042\n\n\u308b\u65b0\u4eba\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":26,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"11 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":26,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u793e\u9577\u306f",
        "np1":"\u79d8\u66f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u65b0\u4eba\u3092",
        "verb":"\u7d39\u4ecb\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":26,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"8 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":26,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5fd7\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3061\u3087\u3063\u3068\u4e00\u7b4b\u7e04\u3067\u306f\u3044\n\n\u304b\u306a\u3044\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u554f\u984c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cea\u554f\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":27,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"5 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":11,
        "Group":27,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5fd7\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3061\u3087\u3063\u3068\u4e00\u7b4b\u7e04\u3067\u306f\u3044\n\n\u304b\u306a\u3044\u554f\u984c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cea\u554f\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":27,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"6 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20,
        "Group":27,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u6b63\u5fd7\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5148\u751f\u306b",
        "np2":"\u554f\u984c\u3092",
        "verb":"\u8cea\u554f\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":27,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"8 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":27,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u79d8\u66f8\u306f",
        "np1":"\u793e\u5185\u3067\u306f\u5acc\u304c\u3089\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u308b\u4e0a\u53f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4ed5\u4e8b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f9d\u983c\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":28,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"12 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18,
        "Group":28,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u79d8\u66f8\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4e0a\u53f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u793e\u5185\u3067\u306f\u5acc\u304c\u3089\u308c\u3066\u3044\n\n\u308b\u4ed5\u4e8b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f9d\u983c\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":28,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"13 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":28,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u79d8\u66f8\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4e0a\u53f8\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4ed5\u4e8b\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f9d\u983c\u3057\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":28,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"14 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22,
        "Group":28,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u592a\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"\u3084\u3063\u3068\u306e\u3053\u3068\u3067\u3088\u3046\u3084\n\n\u304f\u898b\u3064\u3051\u305f\u5f7c\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5ea7\u5e2d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3068\u3063\u3066\u304a\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":29,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"5 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":29,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u592a\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5f7c\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u3084\u3063\u3068\u306e\u3053\u3068\u3067\u3088\u3046\u3084\n\n\u304f\u898b\u3064\u3051\u305f\u5ea7\u5e2d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3068\u3063\u3066\u304a\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":29,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"12 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24,
        "Group":29,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u592a\u90ce\u306f",
        "np1":"\u5f7c\u5973\u306b",
        "np2":"\u5ea7\u5e2d\u3092",
        "verb":"\u3068\u3063\u3066\u304a\u3044\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":29,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"11 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25,
        "Group":29,
        "Item":3
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u30ec\u30dd\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc\u306f",
        "np1":"\u4eca\u65e5\u672c\u4e2d\u3067\u975e\u96e3\u3055\u308c\u3066\n\n\u3044\u308b\u653f\u6cbb\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4e8b\u4ef6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f1d\u3048\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":30,
        "id_letter":"A",
        "math_question":"7 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21,
        "Group":30,
        "Item":1
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u30ec\u30dd\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc\u306f",
        "np1":"\u653f\u6cbb\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4eca\u65e5\u672c\u4e2d\u3067\u975e\u96e3\u3055\u308c\u3066\n\n\u3044\u308b\u4e8b\u4ef6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f1d\u3048\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":30,
        "id_letter":"B",
        "math_question":"5 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17,
        "Group":30,
        "Item":2
    },
    {
        "subj":"\u30ec\u30dd\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc\u306f",
        "np1":"\u653f\u6cbb\u5bb6\u306b",
        "np2":"\u4e8b\u4ef6\u3092",
        "verb":"\u4f1d\u3048\u305f\u3002",
        "id_number":30,
        "id_letter":"C",
        "math_question":"8 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16,
        "Group":30,
        "Item":3
    }
]